Guide to the Woman’s Student Government Association Records, 1919-1974
Duke University. University Archives
- Materials from other colleges, 1959-1967, 1 Box
  - University of Maryland Women Students Handbook, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - University of Vermont WSGA Handbook, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Vassar College Student Handbook, 1959-1960 (Box 17)
- National Student Association, 1 Box
  - NSA Pamphlets File I (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - NSA Pamphlets File II (Box 18)
  - NSA Supplied Pamphlets File III (Box 18)
  - NSA Pamphlets File IV (Box 18)
  - NSA Pamphlets File V (Box 18)
  - University of Maryland File VI-Judiciary Handbooks (Box 18)
- Account books, 1931-1944, 1 Box
  - Debating Club Treasurer's Report, 1936-1937 (Box 19)
  - Duke Nereidians (Box 19)
  - French Club Treasurer's Report, 1936-1937 (Box 19)
  - Pan-Hellenic Treasurer's Report, 1936-1937 (Box 19)
  - Social Services Committee Treasurer Reports, 1936-1937 (Box 19)
  - Social Standards Committee Annual Treasurer's Report, 1936-1937 (Box 19)
  - Social Standards Committee Ledger, 1937-1942 (Box 19)
  - Sophomore Commission Annual Treasurer's Report, 1936-1937 (Box 19)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1937 (Box 19)
  - Town Girl's Club Annual Treasurer's Report (Box 19)
  - Treasurer Reports, 1937 (Box 19)
  - Treasurer Reports, 1942 (Box 19)
  - WSGA Expenses, 1937-1939 (Box 19)
  - Woman's Athletic Association Accounts, 1931-1947 (Box 19)
  - Woman's Athletic/Recreation Association Minutes, 1934-1944 (Box 19)
  - Woman's Athletic Association Treasurer's Report, 1936-1937 (Box 19)
- Student Organizations, 1936-1974, 3 Boxes
  - ASDU (Association of Students of Duke University), 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - ASDU, 1968-1970 (Box 20)
  - Black Problems 1960s and Student Governments, 1960-1970 (Box 20)
  - Class Organizations and Officers, 1963-1969 (Box 20)
  - Constitutions and By-laws Campus Organizations, 1964-1969, undated (Box 20)
  - Eko-L Miscellaneous Records and Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 20)
  - Isotes (Box 20)
  - MSGA - Constitution, undated (Box 20)
  - MSGA - Minutes, 1964-1967 (Box 20)
  - MSGA - Misc., 1952-1966, undated (Box 20)
  - MSGA - Officers, 1966-1969 (Box 20)
  - Methodist Student Fellowship, 1953-1954 (Box 20)
  - Music Study Club (Box 21)
  - Nurses Student Government, 1964-1968 (Box 21)
  - Pan-Hellenic Rush Booklet, 1947-1980(22 folders) (Box 21)
  - PEP Board Constitution, 1955-1957, undated (Box 21)
  - Phi Kappa Delta (Box 21)
  - Sandals Club (Box 21)
  - Student Activities Finances (Box 22)
  - Student Forum (Box 22)
  - Handbook of the Woman's Athletic Association, 1937-1958 (6 folders) (Box 22)
  - Handbook of the Woman's Recreation Association, 1961-1967 (6 folders) (Box 22)
  - The Weekly Post, 1937-1938 (YWCA Publication) (Box 22)
  - Woman's Alliance, 1973-1974 (Box 22)
  - Woman's College Glee Club (Box 22)
  - Woman's College Orchestra (Box 22)
- Oversize, 1925-1937, 1 Box
  - May Day: Program Proposals, Other Schools' Brochures, 1925; 1930 (Oversize-box 23)
  - May Day, 1936-1937 (Box 22)